{
    "subject": "resource/Adam_Soilleux",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Cricketer",
    "human_readable": "Adam Soilleux is a Cricketer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7698250412940979,
            "question": "Is Adam Soilleux a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7681393623352051,
            "question": "How long has Adam Soilleux been playing cricket?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.667123556137085,
            "question": "What sport does Adam Soilleux play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6630352139472961,
            "question": "Which team does Adam Soilleux play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6159957051277161,
            "question": "What is Adam Soilleux known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5704838633537292,
            "question": "Where is Adam Soilleux from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40255868434906006,
            "question": "What is Adam Soilleux's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.323579877614975,
            "question": "What are some of Adam Soilleux's notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25402262806892395,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Adam Soilleux's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.220875084400177,
            "question": "Has Adam Soilleux won any awards in his career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adam Soilleux is a Cricketer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3375_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Adam Soilleux's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3375_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Adam Soilleux's notable achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3375_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Adam Soilleux's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3375_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3375_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided documents, I found that:\n\n* Adam Soilleux is mentioned multiple times as a cricketer, playing for various teams such as MCC Universities, Essex County Cricket Club second XI, and HTCC.\n* He is described as \"captain\" of one of these teams, implying that he holds a position of responsibility in the sport.\n* His skills and achievements on the field are highlighted, further supporting the claim.\n\nTherefore, based on the information provided:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Adam Soilleux playing cricket, including his captaincy and performances for various teams. This supports the statement that Adam Soilleux is a cricketer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}